Guide to the Graduate School Records, 1924-2014 UA.24.01.0001
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1924-1994 and undated
  - History Department, 1956-1958 (Box 28)
  - Holmes, Mary Bynum, 1945 (Box 29)
  - Holton, Holland, 1937-1947 (Box 29)
  - Honor System (Box 29)
  - Master Program, 3 Year (Box 29)
  - Honors - Masters, 1963-1964 (Box 29)
  - Honors - Masters, 1964-1965 (Box 29)
  - Honors - Masters, 1965-1966 (Box 29)
  - Honors - Masters, 1966-1967 (Box 29)
  - Honors - Masters, Continuation (Box 30)
  - Honors - Masters, Copies of Annual Reports (Box 30)
  - Honors - Masters, Correspondence, 1961 Sept.-1962 Sept. (Box 30)
  - Honors - Masters, Genesis at Duke (Box 30)
  - Honors - Masters, Publicity (Box 30)
  - Hoover, Dr. Calvin B., 1948-1949 (Box 30)
  - Hopkins, Institutional Development (Box 30)
  - Hospital Administration, Program in, Proposal, 1961 (Box 30)
  - Hospital Administration (Box 30)
  - House Resident, Men's Graduate Center (Box 30)
  - Housing, Graduate Student (Box 30)
  - Housing Office, 1950-1953 (Box 30)
  - Housing Office, 1958-1959 (Box 30)
  - Hubbell, Jay B., 1943-1949 (Box 30)
  - Humanities and Social Studies, 100-level courses (Box 30)
  - James B. Duke Program, 1959 (Box 30)
  - IBM Matters (Box 30)
  - Inactives (A.M.'s), before, 1945 (Box 31)
  - Income Tax Information (Box 31)
  - Income Tax, Assistants, 1954 (Box 31)
  - Income Tax, Assistants (CSS), 1953 (Box 31)
  - Higher Education, Institute on, 1953 (Box 31)
  - International Education, Institute of, 1933-1950 (Box 31)
  - International Education, Institute, Announcement - Fulbright Law Awards, 1950 (Box 31)
  - International Education, Institute of, Correspondence, 1951-1955 (Box 31)
  - International Education, Institute of, Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box 31)
  - International Education, Institute of, Correspondence, Foreign Students, 1955-1957 (Box 31)
  - International Education, Institute of, 1960 (Box 31)
  - International Education, Institute of, 1961-1968 (Box 32)
  - International Student Exchange, Committee on, Association of Graduate Schools (Box 32)
  - Graduate Faculty, Instructions to, Registration, Bulletin, Regulations, 1940-1942 (Box 32)
  - Intercollegiate Athletics Committee (Box 32)
  - Inter-University, Committee for Economic Research on the South (Box 32)
  - Deans of Graduate Schools, Southern, Conference, 1957-1958 (Box 32)
  - Inter-University, Correspondence (Box 32)
  - Inter-University, Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 33)
  - Inter-University, Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Inter-University, Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 33)
  - Inter-University, Travel Grants (Box 33)
  - Intra-University, Correspondence, 1962-1963 (Box 33)
  - Intra-University, Correspondence, 1963-1964 (Box 33)
  - Intra-University, Correspondence, 1964 (Box 34)
  - Inventory, 1949-1950 (Box 34)
  - Inventory and Supply List (Box 34)
  - Irving, Dr. W. H., 1948 (Box 34)
  - Japan Society (Box 34)
  - Job Folder (Box 34)
  - Job Openings, 1955-1956 (Box 35)
  - Job Opportunities for Students, 1949-1955 (Box 35)
  - Joint Committee on Intellectual Cooperation of Duke University and UNC (Box 35)
  - Jordan, Charles E., 1936-1938 (Box 35)
  - Negro Education, Journal of, 1932-1948 (Box 35)
  - Korstian, C. F., 1931-1948 (Box 35)
  - Kuhlman, Dr. A. F., Librarian, Vanderbilt University Nashville, Tennessee, 1942-1944 (Box 35)
  - Knight, Dr., Correspondence (Box 35)
  - Language Examinations, Placement, 1953 Sept.-1955 (Box 35)
  - Teachers of Science and Mathematics, Laboratory Conference for, 1954 Summer (Box 35)
  - Teachers of Science and Mathematics, Laboratory Conference for, 1954-1955 (Box 35)
  - Language Examinations, Committee on Transfer of (Box 35)
  - Language Examinations, Committee on, 1949 (Box 35)
  - Language Requirements for Masters and Ph.D., 1950-1951 (Box 35)
  - Languages for the Master of Arts Degree, 1949 (Box 35)
  - Lanning, Dr. John Tate, 1948 (Box 35)
  - Laprade, Dr. William Thomas, 1940-1948 (Box 35)
  - Law School Courses, 1950-1951 (Box 35)
  - Ledger, Students Admitted, 1946-1949 (Box 35)
  - Ledger, Admission and Rejection, 1952-1953 (Box 35)
  - Ledger, Admission and Rejections of students, 1953 Summer, Fall (Box 35)
  - Ledger, Admission and Rejections of students, 1950 (Box 35)
  - Leonard, Dr. Henry S., 1941-1948 (Box 35)
  - Library Accessions, 1941-1942 (Box 35)
  - Lisle Fellowship, 1952 (Box 35)
  - Long Range Planning (Box 35)
  - Long Range Planning, Committee (Box 36)
  - Long Range Planning, Committee, Student Enrollment (Box 36)
  - Long Range Planning, Report (Box 36)
  - Manchester, Alan K. (Box 36)
  - Manual of Style, Revised (Box 36)
  - Marine Laboratory, 1955-1956 (Box 36)
  - Markham, C. B., Treasurer, 1949 (Box 36)
  - Markham, C. B., Treasurer, 1944-1949 (Box 36)
  - Martin, Dr. Donald S., 1948 (Box 36)
  - Mathematics Department, 1942-1949 (Box 36)
  - Mathematics Department (Box 36)
  - Master of Art in Teaching, Cooperative Program, 1958-1959 (Box 36)
  - Master of Art in Teaching, Cooperative Program (Box 36)
  - Master of Art in Teaching, Candidates, 1955 Spring, Summer, Fall (Box 36)
  - Master of Art in Teaching, Degree, 1953-1954 (Box 36)
  - Mailing and Addressograph Lists, 1953-1956 (Box 36)
  - Map Survey and Pictures (Box 36)
  - Medical School, 1946-1949 (Box 37)
  - Medical School, Doctoral Programs, 1950-1953 (Box 37)
  - Medical Technicians Course and Medical Graduate Work for A.M. and Ph.D. (Box 37)
  - Microfilm Dissertation Committee (Box 37)
  - Microfilms, University (Box 37)
  - Mid-Term Reports (J.C.R.) (Box 37)
  - Miller Analogies Test Manual (Box 37)
  - Minor, Requirements for, Committee on (Box 37)
  - Development Staff, Minutes (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous, 1950-1955 (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-1956 (Box 37)
  - Miscellaneous, 1957-1960 (Box 38)
  - Modern Language Newsletters and Other Information (Box 38)
  - Sciences, National Academy of; National Research Council, 1956-1957 (Box 38)
  - Sciences, National Academy of; National Research Council, 1957-1961 (Box 38)
  - Foreign Students Advisers, National Association of, 1958-1959 (Box 38)
  - Education Association, National, 1958-1959 (Box 38)
  - Research Council, National, 1949-1955 (Box 38)
  - Science Foundation, National, 1946-1953 (Box 38)
  - Research Council, National (C. J. Lapp), 1947-1948 (Box 38)
  - Science Foundation, National, 1953-1956 (Box 38)
  - Science Foundation, National, 1955-1957 (Box 38)
  - Sciences, National Academy of; National Research Council, 1955 (Box 39)
  - Science Foundation, National, 1954 June (Box 39)
  - Science Foundation, National; Science Institute, 1956-1957 (Box 39)
  - Science Foundation, National; Science Institute, 1957 Spring, Summer (Box 39)
  - Science Institute, 1958 (Box 39)
  - Science Institute, 1959-1960 (Box 39)
  - Negley, Dr. Glenn, 1948 (Box 39)
  - Newsletter, 1955 (Box 39)
  - Nielsen, W. M., 1941-1947 (Box 39)
  - Scholarships, Non-University, 1950-1952 (Box 39)
  - Newsletters (Box 39)
  - Nordheim, Dr. L. W., 1948-1949 (Box 39)
  - North Atlantic Regional Conference, 1955-1956 (Box 39)
  - North Carolina College Conference, 1941-1947 (Box 39)
  - North Carolina State Teacher Education (Box 39)
  - Nursing School, Masters Program (Box 39)
  - Office Plans, New Building, 1953-1954 (Box 39)
  - Scientific Personnel, Office of (Box 39)
  - 100 level courses (Box 40)
  - Areas of University Policy, Original, and Summary of Council Activities, to, 1956 Oct. (Box 40)
  - Parapsychology (Box 40)
  - Parisitology (Box 40)
  - Payroll, Control Sheets (Box 40)
  - Payroll, Fellowships (Box 40)
  - Peaceful Atomic Development, Fund for, 1955 Aug. (Box 40)
  - Perlzweig, W. A., 1945-1949 (Box 40)
  - Personnel, Graduate School Office, 1950-1955 (Box 40)
  - Personnel, Office, 1949-1952 (Box 40)
  - Petitions (Box 40)
  - Phelps-Stokes Fund (Box 40)
  - Ph.D. Census, Procedures (Box 40)
  - Physical Therapy (Box 40)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1949 (Box 40)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1950-1951 (Box 40)
  - Duke Professors who have Supervised Ph.D. Theses Together with the Candidates' Names and the Years the Degrees were Conferred, 1928 June-1953 June (Box 40)
  - Duke Professors who have Supervised Ph.D. Theses Together with the Candidates' Names and the Years the Degrees were Conferred (2 Copies in this box), 1928 June-1953 June (Box 41)
  - Ancient Languages (Box 41)
  - Biochemistry (Box 41)
  - Botany (Box 41)
  - Chemistry (Box 41)
  - Economics (Box 41)
  - Education (Box 41)
  - Education (Ed.D.) (Box 41)
  - English (Box 41)
  - Forestry (Box 41)
  - History (Box 41)
  - Mathematics (Box 41)
  - Microbiology (Box 41)
  - Philosophy (Box 41)
  - Physics (Box 41)
  - Physiology and Pharmacology (Box 41)
  - Political Science (Box 41)
  - Psychology (Box 41)
  - Religion (Box 41)
  - Romance Languages (Box 41)
  - Sociology (Box 41)
  - Zoology (Box 41)
  - Ph.D., Census of (Box 41)
  - Ph.D. Graph Study of Graduates by year, 1928-1953 (Box 42)
  - Ph.D. Publication Committee (Box 42)
  - Philosophy, Department of, 1946-1949 (Box 42)
  - Philosophy, Department of (Box 42)
  - Physics Department, 1947-1948 (Box 42)
  - Physics Department (Box 42)
  - Physiology, Department of, 1941-1947 (Box 42)
  - Physiology, Department of (Box 42)
  - Ph.D. Requirements, Departmental (Box 42)
  - Policy Book "Special Cases" Removed from, 1936-1950 (Box 42)
  - Graduate School, Policies of the, 1939-1952 (Box 42)
  - Graduate. School, Policies and Procedures, Report by Committee (Box 42)
  - Political Science Department, 1947-1949 (Box 42)
  - Political Science Department, 1956-1958 (Box 42)
  - Political Science Department (Box 42)
  - Post-Doctoral Fellowships (Box 42)
  - Predmore, Dr., Personal (Box 43)
  - Predmore, Dr., 1965 (Box 43)
  - Predmore, Dean, Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 43)
  - Predmore, Dean, Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 43)
  - Pre-Doctoral, 1949 (Box 43)
  - Glasson, Dean, Reports "Graduate School History", through, 1924-1932 (Box 43)
  - President's Reports, 1949-1950 (Box 43)
  - President's Reports, 1950-1951 (Box 43)
  - President's Reports, 1954-1955 (Box 43)
  - President's Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 43)
  - President's Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 43)
  - President's Reports, 1957-1958 (Box 43)
  - President's Reports, 1958-1959 (Box 44)
  - Annual Reports to the President, 1959-1962 (Box 44)
  - Presiding Officers, 1954 (Box 44)
  - Printed Forms (Box 44)
  - Teacher Education, Programs of (Box 44)
  - Proposals (Box 44)
  - Provost's Staff (Box 44)
  - Psychology, 1956-1958 (Box 44)
  - Public Health Service, 1966 Jan. (Box 45)
  - Purchasing Department, 1949-1950 (Box 45)
  - Publication Fund, 1949-1956 (Box 45)
  - Publicity (Box 45)
  - Questionnaires, 1940-1942 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire (A), 1953 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire (B), 1953 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire (C), 1953 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire (D), 1953 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire (E), 1953 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire (F), 1953 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire (G), 1953 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire (H), 1953 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire (I), 1953 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire (J), 1953 (Box 45)
  - Questionnaire (K), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (L), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (Mc), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (M), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (N), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (O), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (P), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (Q), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (R), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (S), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (T), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (U), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (V), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (W), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaire (X-Y-Z), 1953 (Box 46)
  - Questionnaires, to be typed (Box 46)
  - Questionnaires, New (Box 46)
  - Questionnaires, Old (Box 46)
  - Questionnaires, 1952-1955 (Box 47)
  - Questionnaires, 1955-1958 (Box 47)
  - Questionnaires, 1958-1960 (Box 47)
  - Racial Segregation at Duke (Box 47)
  - Radiation Biology, 1956-1957 (Box 47)
  - Rankin Committee (Box 47)
  - Recommendations for Positions (Box 47)
  - Refund Letter $50 thesis deposit - When publication app. other copies in form drawer and cabinet for INT's supplies (Box 47)
  - Letters written when reprints submitted which give $50 refund for thesis deposit or waive deposit before Graduation (Box 47)
  - Regional Council for Education, 1948 (Box 47)
  - Registrars Convention, 1952 (Box 47)
  - Registration, 1950-1955 (Box 47)
  - Registration Procedure (Box 47)
  - Religion, 1956-1958 (Box 47)
  - Religion (Box 47)
  - Religion, Executive Council in (Box 47)
  - Ph.D. Recommenders, Replies, 1955-1956 (Box 48)
  - Reprints and/or Books Carried to Library, 1949 (Box 48)
  - Reprints: Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 48)
  - Research Assistants, 1953 (Box 48)
  - Research Statement, General Board Education, 1938 (Box 48)
  - Election Returns, Letters and Memoranda, 1956-1957 (Box 48)
  - Manual of Style, Revised, 1954-1955 (Box 48)
  - Advanced Degrees, Revision in Requirements for, Graduate. Faculty Meeting, 1958 Apr. (Box 48)
  - Riecken, H. (Box 48)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1936-1954 (Box 48)
  - Rockefeller Foundation, Dr. Otto Nathan (010-F19-2 Salary Payments; 010-F19-8 Traveling Expenses), 1941-1944 (Box 48)
  - Romance Language, Results of Romance Language Examinations (Box 48)
  - Romance Languages, Department of, 1946-1949 (Box 48)
  - Romance Languages, Department of (Box 49)
  - Sabbatical Committee of University Council, 1953 (Box 49)
  - Classes, Schedule of, 1948-1956 (Box 49)
  - Course Offerings, Schedules, 1955-1956 (Box 49)
  - Course Offerings, Schedules, 1956 Summer (Box 49)
  - Classes, Schedule of, 1956-1957 (Box 49)
  - Courses, Schedule of, 1958-1959 (Box 50)
  - Courses, Schedule of, 1959-1960 (Box 50)
  - Courses, Schedule of, 1960-1961 (Box 50)
  - Courses, Schedule of, 1961-1962 (Box 50)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1952 (Box 50)
  - Religion, School of, 1944-1949 (Box 50)
  - Law School Conference, 1954 (Box 50)
  - Schools, Education, etc., Problems, 1954-1955 (Box 50)
  - Science and Mathematics Teachers, Summer Program, 1956 (Box 50)
  - Selective Service (Box 50)
  - Shepard, James E., 1939-1941 (Box 50)
  - Shepard, President James E., North Carolina College for Negroes, Durham, N.C., 1944-1945 (Box 50)
  - Siebert Scholarship, 1947-1948 (Box 50)
  - Smith, Dr. H. Shelton, 1948 (Box 50)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1939-1949 (Box 50)
  - Social Science Research Council, 1949-1953 (Box 50)
  - Social Science Research Council (Box 50)
  - Sociology, Department, 1947-1949 (Box 51)
  - Sociology, Department (Box 51)
  - Sociology, Problem (Box 51)
  - South Atlantic Bulletin, 1936-1947 (Box 51)
  - South Atlantic Bulletin, 1951-1955 (Box 51)
  - Southern Association Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1941-1947 (Box 51)
  - Southern Association Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1953 Nov. 30-1953 Dec. 4 (Box 51)
  - Southern Association Colleges and Secondary Schools, Louisville, Kentucky, 1954 Nov. 29-1954 Dec. 2 (Box 51)
  - Southern Association Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1955-1956 (Box 51)
  - Southern Association, Committee on Graduate Standards, 1955 Oct. (Box 51)
  - Southern Economic Association (Box 51)
  - Southern Fellowship Fund, 1954-1956 (Box 51)
  - Southern Fellowship Fund, 1956-1958 (Box 51)
  - Southern Fellowship Fund (Box 51)
  - Southern Fellowship Fund, 1958-1959 (Box 51)
  - Southern Fellowship Fund, 1959-1961 (Box 52)
  - Southern Historical Association, 1950 (Box 52)
  - Southern Regional Education, 1949-1956 (Box 52)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 1956 (Box 52)
  - Southern Regional Education Board (Box 52)
  - Southern Regional Education Board Meeting Goals, 1961 (Box 52)
  - Speech Materials (Box 52)
  - Spengler, Prof. J. J., 1956 (Box 52)
  - Spengler, J. J., 1946-1947 (Box 52)
  - State Research Staff, Department of, 1952 (Box 52)
  - Statistics, Courses and Registration, 1954-1957 (Box 52)
  - Statistics, Awards (MEH), 1957-1958 (Box 52)
  - Statistics, Course and Seminar Hours Completed for Ph.D. and Ed.D. Degrees (MEH), 1952-1958 (Box 52)
  - Statistics, Courses and Registration (MEH), 1954-1957 (Box 52)
  - Statistics, Enrollment (MEH), 1956-1957 (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Enrollment (MEH), 1957-1958 (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Degrees Conferred (MEH), 1957 June, 1957 Sept. (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Degrees Conferred (MEH), 1958 June, 1958 Sept. (Box 53)
  - Statistics, James B. Duke Fellowships (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Faculty, Student Ratios (MEH), 1951-1956 (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Incompletes (MEH) (Box 53)
  - Tuition and Fees, Programs, Degrees Conferred; Other Universities (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Registration (MEH), 1958-1959 (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Summary Statistics on Course and Seminar Hours Completed for Doctoral Degrees (MEH), 1952 June-1958 June (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Time Elapsed for Preliminary Examination and for Presentation of Dissertation (MEH) (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Woodrow Wilson and National Science Foundation Predoctoral Fellows (MEH), 1958-1959 (Box 53)
  - Statistical Report, Summer Session, 1953 (Box 53)
  - Statistical Report, Summer Session, 1954 (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Summer Session (MEH), 1956 (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Summer Session (MEH), 1957 (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Summer Session (MEH), 1958 (Box 53)
  - Statistics, Survey by States and Countries of Distribution of Applications, 1952-1954 (Box 53)
  - Ph.D. Candidates, Status of; Replies to letter to D.G.S., 1956 May (Box 53)
  - Student Directory, 1947 (Box 53)
  - Student Health and Insurance, 1955 (Box 53)
  - Student Lists, 1951-1954 (Box 53)
  - Student Lists, Summer School, 1948 (Box 53)
  - Student Lists, 1928-1946 (Box 54)
  - Student Lists, Official, 1949 Sept. (Box 54)
  - Student Lists, 1950 Summer (Box 54)
  - Student Lists, 1954-1958 (Box 55)
  - Student Lists, 1956-1957 (Box 55)
  - Student Lists, Entering Student by Major (For Departmental Reviews), 1957-1962 (Box 55)
  - Student Lists, 1958-1959 (Box 55)
  - Student Lists, 1959-1960 (Box 55)
  - IBM Student List, Summer School, 1960 (Box 55)
  - Student Lists, 1960-1961 (Box 55)
  - Student Lists (2 Folders), 1960-1961 (Box 56)
  - Students, Master List of, 1961 Spring (Box 56)
  - Student Lists, Summer School, 1960-1961 (Box 56)
  - Students, Master List of, 1962 Spring (Box 56)
  - Student Lists (Box 56)
  - Students, Master List of, 1962 summer (Box 56)
  - Students, Master List of, 1962 Fall (Box 56)
  - Students, Master List of, 1963 Spring (Box 56)
  - Students, Master List of, 1963 Fall (Box 56)
  - Student Lists, Official; Graduate School, to, 1949 Sept. (Box 57)
  - Student Lists, Foreign, 1955-1957 (Box 57)
  - Student Loan Division (Box 57)
  - Students by Major Department, 1962-1963 (Box 57)
  - UNESCO, Study Abroad, 1956 (Box 57)
  - Foreign Languages, Substitutions, 1954 (Box 57)
  - Student Health Walker Agency, 1962-1964 (Box 57)
  - Williams Summer Institute (Box 57)
  - Summer School, Scholarships (Box 57)
  - Scholarship Luncheon, Summer, 1954 (Box 57)
  - Summer Session, Catalog, 1949-1954 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session, Committee and Following, 1953 July 22 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session, Scholarship Material, 1955 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session, 1938 (Box 58)
  - Summer School, 1939-1949 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session, Graduates, 1947 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session, Graduates, First and Second Terms, 1949 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session (2 Folders), 1948 (Box 58)
  - Summer School, 1st Term Graduates and Correspondence, 1949 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session, 1949 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session, Scholarships, 1953 (Box 58)
  - Summer School, Correspondence, 1950-1954 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session, 1952 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session, 1955 (Box 58)
  - Summer Session, 1956 (Box 59)
  - Summer Scholars' Luncheon, 1955 (Box 59)
  - Summer Session, 1957 (Box 59)
  - Summer Session, 1958 (Box 59)
  - Summer School, Lists; Names of Students and Usual Information, 1958 (Box 59)
  - Summer Session, Correspondence, 1959-1960 (Box 59)
  - Supplies and Office Equipment, 1953 (Box 59)
  - Sydnor, Dr. Charles S., 1948 (Box 59)
  - Teacher Training Program (College), 1939-1950 (Box 59)
  - Tennessee Eastman Company, 1955-1956 (Box 59)
  - Thesis Carried to Library (I), 1928-1950 (Box 60)
  - Thesis Deposit Forfeitures and Thesis Fund (Box 60)
  - Thesis Carried to Library (II), 1951 (Box 60)
  - Thesis, Subjects, 1927-1937 (Box 60)
  - Thesis, Subjects, 1938-1946 (Box 60)
  - Thesis, Subjects, 1947-1948 (Box 60)
  - Thesis, 1959-1962 (Box 60)
  - Thesis; Publication and Publishers Academic Hoods, Caps, and Gowns, 1941 (Box 60)
  - Traffic Commission, 1952-1955 (Box 61)
  - Traffic Commission, 1957 (Box 61)
  - Training of College Teachers (Box 61)
  - Transcript Policies, 1952 (Box 61)
  - Travel Advances and Reimbursements, 1955-1956 (Box 61)
  - Travel Advances and Reimbursements (Box 61)
  - Travel Expenses, 1948-1949 (Box 61)
  - Travel Expense, 1950-1952 (Box 61)
  - Travel Awards, 1961-1962 (Box 61)
  - Travel Awards, 1963 (Box 61)
  - Triennial Review, Anatomy (Box 61)
  - Triennial Review, Pre-Clinical (Box 61)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Papers, 1962 (Box 61)
  - Tuition (Proposal for Paying) at Other Institutions for Children, Duke Faculty (Box 61)
  - Undergraduate Faculty Council (2 Folders) (Box 61)
  - UNESCO, 1952 (Box 61)
  - U.S. Steel Foundation, Inc. (Box 61)
  - University Committees, 1950-1955 (Box 61)
  - University Council, 1953-1954 (Box 61)
  - University Council, Committee on Functioning of, 1956 Nov. (Box 61)
  - University Council, Committee Reports; Extra Copies and Drafts (Box 62)
  - University Council, General Information (Box 62)
  - University Council, Research (Box 62)
  - University Council, Membership (Box 62)
  - University Council, Minutes, 1954-1960 (Box 62)
  - University Council (Box 62)
  - University of North Carolina, Correspondence, 1951-1956 (Box 62)
  - University Organization, 1951 (Box 62)
  - University's Relationship to Elementary and Secondary Teachers, 1951-1954 (Box 62)
  - University Schedule Committee (Box 62)
  - Vacation Schedule, Office, 1955-1956 (Box 62)
  - Vacation Schedules, Summer, 1959 (Box 62)
  - Veterans Administration, 1946-1948 (Box 62)
  - Veterans Administration, 1949-1951 (Box 62)
  - Veterans Enrollment, 1956-1960 (Box 63)
  - Veterans, information concerning, 1946 (Box 63)
  - Veterans, 1950-1955 (Box 63)
  - Visits to Other Colleges, 1954 (Box 63)
  - Visits to Other Colleges, Prof. Rankin, 1955 Feb. (Box 63)
  - Visits to Other Colleges, Prof. Ward (Virginia), 1955 Feb. (Box 63)
  - Visits to Other Colleges (Princeton-Columbia, Possible Visit to MIT), 1955-1956 (Box 63)
  - Visits to Southern Colleges, J. T. Lanning, 1953 Feb. (Box 63)
  - Visits to Northern Universities, 1952 Fall (Box 63)
  - Visitors, 1950-1955 (Box 63)
  - Vitae (Box 64)
  - Vollmer, Dr. C., 1948 (Box 64)
  - Walker Insurance Agency (Box 64)
  - Walker Insurance Agency, Student Insurance, 1957-1960 (Box 64)
  - Wannamaker, Dean W. H., 1937-1941 (Box 64)
  - Ward, Dr. Charles E., 1948 (Box 64)
  - White, Dr. Newman I., 1940 (Box 64)
  - Whitford, W. E., 1946-1948 (Box 64)
  - Whitford, W. E., 1953-1955 (Box 64)
  - Williamsburg International Assembly (Box 65)
  - Withdrawal Notice, Possible Revision of (Box 65)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Program (Gross), 1952-1956 (Box 65)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship, 1952-1957 (Box 65)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship, Selection Committee (Prof. Predmore), 1956 (Box 65)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship (Box 65)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Foundation, National, 1959 (Box 66)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Foundation, National, 1960-1961 (Box 66)
  - Woodrow Wilson, 1961-1962 (Box 66)
  - Woodrow Wilson, Summer, 1962 (Box 66)
  - Woodrow Wilson, Dissertation Fellowship Program, 1962-1963 (Box 66)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship, 1962-1963 (Box 66)
  - Woodrow Wilson, Summer, 1963 (Box 66)